Guide to the Burton Hall Papers WAG.087
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Union Democracy Cases
  - Subseries C: Maritime
    - International Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots (IOMM&P)
      - 72 Civ 4486; Defendants' Memorandum; Affidavit, T. O'Callaghan, Dec 13, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Reply Affidavit, Dec 15, 1972; Judicial Order, Hon. Irving H. Saypol, Feb 23, 1973, 1972, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - Usery, Department of Labor v. IOMM&P; 72 Civ. 5031 (CBM); (77 Civ. 8341 / 8408 /; 6206/ 6207); Index, p. 4; U.S. Attorney's Rule 9(g) Statement, Dec 13, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Hodgson, Department of Labor v. IOMM&P, International; Maritime Div. International Longshoremen's Association; 72 Civ. 5031 (CBM); Memorandum of Law in Support of Plaintiffs' Motion for Summary Judgment, undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - Deposition in Opposition to Motion, Jan 17, 1975; Notice of Motion, Jan 22, 1975; Affidavit,Jan 22, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, Feb 6, 1975; Memorandum in Opposition to Proposed Settlement (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Court Appearance, May 25, 1977; Memorandum, Opinion & Order, CBM, Je 13, 1977;Correspondence, Je 14, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence, Je 16 1977; Memorandum of Law in Opposition to Certification of Court's Order (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Court Appearance Je 23 1977; Deposition July 29 1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Secretary of Labor's Memorandum; of Law in Opposition to Motion, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Affidavits on Intervention July 1977; Appellee-Union's Memorandum; Docket No. 77-6206;(formerly 77-8341) (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence Je 13 1978; Correspondence, BH to DOL; Election protest, with; Affidavit,Gene Laski (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Affidavit in Support of Certification, Nov 30, 1978; Department of Labor, Dec 7, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Exhibits in Support of Secretary's Motion for Certification, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Exhibits (continued), undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Sheldon, Lloyd, Ofelt, Jack, v. Lowen, Robert & O'Callaghan, Thomas; 73 Civ. 1976; (72 Civ. 3831); Index; Correspondence, Dec 14, 1972; Deposition, Aug 23, 1973, 1972-1976 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, Sept 29, 1975; Notice of Counter-Service, July 29, 1982, 1975-1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Raymond, Matthew v. IOMM&P & Local 88; 74 Civ. 5685 (LPG); Telegram, Summons, Dec 26, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Stipulation, Jan 22, 1975; Correspondence, Je 7, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Jan 2, 1976; Correspondence, BH, Nov 17, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Stipulation of Facts, Jan, 1977; Correspondence, Mar 26, 1978, 1977, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Nereaux, Henry, Soto, Victor, Holdeman, Arthur v. O'Callaghan, Thomas, IOMM&P, Off-Shore Division, & International Ballot Committee; Index No. 00138/75; Correspondence, Jan 2, 1974; Correspondence, BH, Jan 17, 1975, 1974, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Order to Show Cause Jan 20 1975; Draft of Ballot on Off-Shore Division; Referendum (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Case No. 30-7355 (73); 1977 Election - Offshore Division (Sequel to Usery,; DoL v. IOMM&P); DoL Correspondence, Jan 4, 1977; Dol Correspondence, Apr 1, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - DoL Correspondence May 12 1976; Instructions to Ballot Committee, 1965 Convention, 1965, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Flyer, "A Blatant Conspiracy," Jan 5, 1978; Correspondence with Note, Mar 29, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Pre-Election Protests, Mar 28, 1978; Correspondence to BH, Dec 4, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Johnson, Gerald, Hemming, Charles, et. al. v. Scavo, Frank, International; President, Off-Shore Division, IOMM&P; 77 Civ.489 (LPG); Correspondence, May 14, 1979; Opposition to Attorney's Fees (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, Jan 10, 1980; Correspondence, Order, Aug 4, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Soto, Victor, Seybert, John v. IOMM&P & Off-Shore Membership Group; 78 Civ. 5300; Complaint, Nov 1, 1978; Affidavit, Dec 19, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - Answer, Dec 20 1978; Findings of Fact, Je 20, 1979, 1978, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - Plaintiffs' Exhibits, Resolution, Nov 8, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - Defendants' Exhibits, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - Documents, Ballots, Resolution, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - Nereaux, Henry & Lazar, H. v. Seybert, J. & Soto, V., Washington Street Marine Officers Corp.; 05086/79; Order to Show Cause, Mar 18, 1979; Summons & Complaint, Judicial Memorandum, July, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Soto, V., Pettrazzulo, Joseph, et. al. v. IOMM&P & Nereaux, H.; 80 Civ. 4471 (LWP); Minutes, Report, May 8 1980; Memorandum of Law, pp. 5-11, Aug 13, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Plaintiffs' Reply Memorandum (Draft), Aug 14, 1980; Affidavit, 8-Sep-80 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Examination, pp. 357-457, July 8 1981; Pre-Trial Order, Re- Draft, Oct, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Laski, Gene, Vecchione, Philip, et. al. v. IOMM&P; 80 Civ. 4906; Summons, Aug 25, 1980; Memorandum in Opposition, Sept 5, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Affidavit, G. Laski, Sept 9, 1980; Exhibits, Documents (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Morales, Jose v. Lowen, R. & IOMM&P; Index No. 16471-80; 1980 Election Challenge; (Related to 80 Civ. 4906); Hand-Written Challenge; Court Documents (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Grievance - Discharge & Shipping Rules, John Lombard 1971 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Grievances - Pension, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Grievances - Wages, George H. Balser, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Constitutions, By-Laws, IOMM&P & Local 88, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Proposed Constitution, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Resolutions, Amendments, Reports, Sample Ballots, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - LM-2s, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1972, 1978-81, 1972, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Constitutional Convention, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Constitutional Convention, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - IOMM&P 65th Convention, Partial Transcript, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - General Executive Board Meeting, Nov, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Federal Credit Union, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Local 88, Trustee Silverman's Election Plan, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Minutes, Local 88 Membership Meetings (#1), undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Local 88 Minutes (#2), undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - Minutes, Local 88 Executive Committee Meetings, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Rank-and-File Literature (Dated), undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Rank-and-File Literature (Undated) (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - IOMM&P Election Challenges, Local 88 - #1, 1960-67, 1960-1967 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Local 88 Election Challenges - #2, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - Local 88 Election Challenges - #3, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - Constitutional & 1970 Election Challenges - #4, 1970, 1971, 1973, 1970-1973 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Local 88 Election Challenges - #5 (See 72 Civ. 5031), 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Off-Shore Division Election Challenges - #6, 1975-1979 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - IOMM&P Election Challenges - #7, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Documents - General, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Merchant Marine, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Ricks, James, ARA & IOMM&P; NLRB Case 20-CB-5066, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Ricks, James, NLRB Case 2-CB-9169; Unfair Labor Practice, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Ricks, James, NLRB, Discharge, Keystone Shipping, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - McClish v. ARA & IOMM&P (Fiduciary), undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Pension Trust-Investment Account, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - McClish, C.L. ARA & IOMM&P Election Appeal, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - McClish Election Appeal, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - McClish Election Appeal, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - McClish Election Appeal, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - McClish - Rank-and-File Flyers, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - McClish Correspondence, Documents, Ballots, Resolutions (Susan Jennik, Hall, Clifton & Schwartz, McClish's Attorney), undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Brock, Wm., Secretary of Labor, Department of Labor & Vallis, John, v. IOMM&P & ARA; Correspondence, Je 10, 1981; Correspondence, Dec 29, 1984, 1981, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, Jan 31, 1985; Correspondence, Dec 14, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, Jan 21, 1986; Memorandum in Support of Appellant (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Informal Brief, Correspondence, Sept 5, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Affidavit, J. Vallis, Dec 9, 1985; Brief, Plaintiffs- Appellants (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Trial Transcript (Partial), Civil Action No. B85-3444, undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - News Clipping, Jan 29, 1986; Constitution, By-Laws, Ballot (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - IOMM&P & ARA Pension & Welfare Benefits - Brannick, Bruce, undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - IOMM&P & ARA Medical Costs - Thomas, Norman R., undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - IOMM&P & ARA Vacation Pay - Vallis, John, undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Hayes, John N. & Larsen, James, v. IOMM&P (Paul A. Levy, Esq. for Plaintiffs), 1987 (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Soto, V. et. al. v. Bracco, C.J., Pension Parity (See Pension File - IOMM&P, 1969-1974) (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - United States Lines, Inc. v. M/V Jose Luis Aznar (V. Soto - Salvage); 72 Civ. 7583, undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - Wallace, Oscar v. IOMM&P & Lowen, Robert, President; 80 Civ. 4699 (EW), undated (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Seafarers' International Union (SIU)
      - Cole v. Hall, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Preliminary Injunction, Jan, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Defendants' Affidavits, Exhibits, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Reply Affidavit, BH, Jan 28, 1964; Proposed Order, Apr, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, BH, May 1, 1964; Amended Complaint (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Order of Injunction, John F. Dooling, Jr. U.S.D.J., May 27, 1964; Correspondence, Je 1, 1965, 1964, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Amended Answer to Plaintiff's Objections to Interrogatories, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Affidavit, BH, Oct 6, 1966, Affidavit, Oct 21, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Memorandum of Law, Judicial Order, Walter Bruchhausen, U.S.D.J., Dec 2, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Affidavit, Exhibits, Jan 11 1967; Retainer Statement, Sept 25, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Stipulation, July 12, 1968; Deposition, J. Cole, pp. 1-201, July 12, 1968, Aug 12, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Notice of Court, Oct 10 1968; Corrections to Deposition, Nov 19, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Deposition of J. Cole; pp. 345-398, Nov 29 1968; Correspondence, BH, Sept 10, 1969, 1968, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Trial Transcript, pp. 1-263, Jan 12, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Trial Transcript, pp. 264-473, Jan 13, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Trial Transcript, pp. 474-680a, Jan 19, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Trial Transcript pp. 681-907, Jan 20, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Trial Transcript pp. 908-1119, Jan 21, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - SEATRAIN LINES, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - Plaintiff's Post-Trial Memorandum, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - Defendants' Trial Memorandum, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, Mar 18, 1971; Correspondence, Dec 9, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - Appellate Briefs, Appendix, Docket No. 72-1003, undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Appeals Court Briefs; Decision, U.S. Court of Appeals, Je 22, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence, Jan 12, 1972; Correspondence, Dec 18, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, BH, Jan 12, 1973; Correspondence, BH to J. Cole, Dec 20, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Memorandum of Decision & Order, Jan 15, 1974; Satisfaction of Judgment, Feb 28, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Rank-and-File Literature, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Exhibits (Partial), undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Merchant Marine ("Editorial Reaction to the Norris Report"), undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (ILWU)
      - 4th Amended Complaint, May 17, 1965; Transcript (Partial), Jan 23, 1974, 1965, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Apr 12 1976; Interrogatories (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Findings of Fact, Aug 27, 1976; Proposed Findings (Annotated) (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Appellants' Briefs - 2, including S. Weir's File Copy; No. 77- 1398 / No. 20,719, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - No. 42284 GBH / No. 77-1398; Opinion, U.S. Court of Appeals, Feb 8, 1980; Petition for Rehearing, Mar 7, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Briefs (Printed); Petition for Writ; Motion for Teamsters for a Democratic Union, et. al.; Amici Curiae in Support of Petition, BH and Staughton Lynd, of Counsel, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Longshoremen's Defense Committee, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Amicus Brief, Workers Defense League, Supporting Documents; Amici Briefs (Other), undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - ILWU Documents - #1, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - ILWU Documents - #2, undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Legal Review, etc., undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - International Longshoremen's Association (ILA)
      - Swirski, Frank, et. al., Local 9 v. Randazzo, Joseph, President, Local 9, ILA, undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - King, Gilbert M. et. al., Local 1476 v. Randazzo, Joseph, Sugar Workers Council, ILA; 64 C. 605 - #1, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - King v. Randazzo - #2; Docket No. 29267; Brief & Appendix for Appellants-Cross, Appellees; Decision, May 24, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - Sucrest Corp. & Sugar Workers Council, ILA, Local 1476; NLRB 1969 (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - LiButti, Peter et. al., v. DiBrizzi, Alex., Pres., Local 920, ILA; Docket No. 29206 - #1, undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - Libutti v. DiBrizzi - #2, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - ILA - Waterfront Commission; Randolph, Fred (Discipline), 1964 28 Local 333, ILA (Tugboats); NLRB Case 1981-82, 1964, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - National Maritime Union (NMU)
      - Morrissey, James M. -; Pre-Morrissey Election; Challenges, NMU 1960-61, 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, Jan 6, 1966; NMU PILOT (Special Extra) (Box 16, Folder 30)
      - Curran's NMU Headquarters v. the Men at Sea (Nation) Jan 30, 1967; Correspondence, Aug 23, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 31)
      - The Call Mar 1968; Deposition, BH, July 23, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 32)
      - Notice of Motion, July 15, 1968; Decision (Printed), U.S. Court of Appeals, W. Wirtz, Department of Labor v. NMU (Box 16, Folder 33)
      - The Call Aug 1, 1968; Telegram (Box 16, Folder 34)
      - Morrissey v. NMU, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 35)
      - Memoranda of law, Briefs, U.S. Court of Appeals (650 F 2d 1267), undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
      - NMU Staff Pension Plan 1981 (Box 16, Folder 37)
      - Padilla, Joseph; (Plaintiff in Morrissey v. NMU); NLRB - 2-CB- 4439; - 2-CA-11430, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Firmin-Guyon, Gaston; NLRB - 2-CB-4616 1967 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Firmin-Guyon, Gaston; NLRB - 2-CB-4616, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Grace Lines - NLRB Cases, NMU Litigation, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Moore-McCormack Lines, Inc., NLRB - 29-CB-2872 1977 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - United States Lines, Inc., NLRB Cases - Jackson, Curtis; 2-CA- 10086; 2-CB-4054, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - United States Lines Inc.; Estis, August 1985-86, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - NMU Grievances, 1965-71, 1965-1971 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - NMU Grievance, Sancho, Joseph, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - NMU Background Literature, Rank-and-File Flyers, Press Clippings, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Subseries D: Transportation
    - Transport Workers Union (TWU)
      - O'Hara, James T. v. Corapi, Ralph, President, Local 101, TWU; 81-7939, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Goldberg, Arthur v. Hall, Sonny, President, Local 100, TWU; 87 Civ. 8025; Correspondence, Mar 13, 1986; Correspondence, Nov 10, 1987, 1986, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Order to Show Cause Memorandum in Support of Motion, Nov 10, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Memorandum of Law, Local 100, Exhibits, Nov 18, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - Reply Affidavit, Nov, 1987; Correspondence, Dec 4, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Answer, Defendant, Jan, 1988; Affirmation, BH, Mar 25, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - 87 Civ. 8025 / 88 - 7850; Memorandum of Law, & Order, Vincent L. Broderick, USDJ, July 28, 1988; Reply Brief, Local 100 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Joint Appendix 88-7850, undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Goldberg, Arthur, Local 100, TWU Election Challenge, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - Grievance, Local 100, TWU, Castellana, R., 1981 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - International Association of Machinists (IAM)
      - Turner, William v. Air Transport Lodge 1894, IAM; 77 Civ. 1146 (MAC); Turner's Appeal of Trial Board's Decision; Plaintiff's Reply Memorandum, Oct 20, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - Notice of Appeal, Apr 28, 1978; Statement of Costs, Dec 19, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - Petition for En Banc Review, U.S. Court of Appeals, 78-7212; Release of Plaintiff's Claim for Attorney's Fee Award, Apr 23, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 31)
      - Brief of Plaintiff-Appellee; Reply Brief, undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - Petition for Writ of Certiorari; IAM Brief of Respondent in Opposition, undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - Gordon, Carl, et. al. v. Winpisinger, William, IAM, 82 Civ. 0529; Rank-and-File Flyers, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - Convention Minutes, 1975-1979 (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - IAM Annuity Plan for TWA Machinists, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 36)
      - Trial Transcript, pp. 1-115; Exhibit Documents, undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence, May 25 1966; Memos, IAM, Mar 9, 1976, 1966, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, Memos, Report, IAM, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, Memos, IAM, Mar 29, 1978, Dec 1, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - IAM Trial Transcript, pp. 1-292, July 31, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, IAM, Jan 16, 1979, Nov 9, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, IAM, C. Gordon to BH, Jan 6 1982, Aug 25, 1986, 1982, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Labor Relations Reference Manual Gordon v. Winpisinger, Civil Cover Sheet, Mar 2, 1982; Correspondence, BH, Je 16, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Request for Production of Documents, Je 22 1982; Defendant's Response to Plaintiffs' Request, Aug 23, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Defendant's Motion for Summary Judgment with Memorandum in Support, Aug 23, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, BH Aug 25 1982; Correspondence Oct 21 1982 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Plaintiffs' Notice of Motion for Order, Oct 27, 1982; Plaintiffs' Sur-Reply &; Reply Memorandum, Correspondence, Nov 17, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Nov 23, 1982; Deposition, C. Gordon, pp. 1-110, Nov 5, 1982; Correspondence, Feb 12, 1983, 1982, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Defendant's Memorandum; Supplementary Memorandum in Opposition, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, Dec 23, 1982; Transcript, Deposition, pp. 1- 214 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, Feb 10 1983; Plaintiffs' Objections to Magistrate's Report (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, Sept 13 1983; Correspondence, BH, Dec 29, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Memorandum & Order, Joseph M. McLaughlin, DJ, Jan 27, 1984; Correspondence, Dec 10, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Amended Standard Referral Order, Jan 5, 1985; Correspondence, BH, May 22, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - Plaintiffs' Statement under Rule 3(g), Je 4, 1985; Revised Pre-Trial Order, Oct 23, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, Dec 20, 1985; Petition for Permission to Appeal, Aug 1, 1986, 1985, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, BH Apr 29, 1987; Transcript, Deposition, Michael Warfield, pp. 1-120, Nov 16, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Transcript, M. Warfield, pp. 121-171, Nov 17, 1987; Correspondence, Dec 19, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Order, David F. Jordon, U.S. Magistrate, Jan 25, 1988; Transcript, Carl Gordon, pp. 1-52 (Corrected), Nov 16, 1987, 1987, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Pre-Trial Scheduling Order, Mar 1, 1988; Correspondence, Plaintiffs to BH (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Subseries E: Entertainment
    - American Federation of Musicians (AFM)
      - Clean Slate By-Laws, Resolutions, Campaign; Gurton, Al, Rothstein, Murray, Glasel, John et. al., Local 802, AFM; Minutes of By-laws Meeting; Court Order, May 11, 1964; Edited Transcript of By-laws Meeting, Je 1, 1964; Appeal, Gurton & Rothstein, May 18, 1964; Transcripts, By-laws Meetings (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Musicians Voice; Opposition Leaflets, Reports, Notes, Resolutions, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Gurton, Al, Rothstein, Murray, et. al. v. Manuti, Al, President, & Arons, Max, Secretary, Local 802, AFM, 64 Civ. 1158; Order to Show Cause Apr 1964; Judicial Opinion, May 11, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Gurton, Al, et. al. v. Arons, Max, Local 802, AFM, 64 Civ. 2292 (Cross-Referenced with 64 Civ. 2291); Deposition, J. Glasel, July, 1964; Opinion, U.S.D.J. Tenney; Notice of Appeal Sept, 1964; Index, Oct, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Guarnaccia, Rudolph, Rothstein, Murray, et. al. v. Kenin, Herman, President, Ballard, Stanley, Secretary, et. al., AFM, 64 Civ. 2291; Complaint; Index to Consolidated Record on Appeal; Correspondence, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Docket No. 29232 (2292/2291); Brief & Appendix for Appellees; Motion for Staying Election, Feb 11, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (Moved - See Folder 21), undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Rothstein, Murray, Gurton, Al, Glasel, John, Guarnaccia, Rudy, et. al. v. Manuti, Al, et. al., Local 802, AFM; 64 Civ. 890; Summons & Complaint, Mar 19, 1964; Motion to Reargue Apr 28, 1964; Supporting Memorandum (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Notice of Motion Restraining Defendants, Je 5, 1964; Judicial Order Je 19, 1964; Annotated Fact Sheet, "The False Messsiahs," Sept, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Manuti, Al v. Rothstein, Murray, Supreme Court of the State of New York; Fact Sheet, Messiahs," Sept, 1964; Summons & Complaint, Sept 28, 1964; Notice of Deposition, Nov 30, 1964. (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Deposition, M. Rothstein, Feb 2, 1965; Stipulation for Discontinuance, Oct 7, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Rothstein, Murray v. Shapiro, Sol, et. al., Local 802 AFM; Musicians Voice - "Plaintiffs Demand for a Bill of Particulars," Jan 11, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Arons, Al v. Rothstein, Murray, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Carroll, Joseph, et. al. v. AFM & Local 802, AFM; U.S. Court of Appeals, Docket No. 30445-46; Judicial Decision, Jan 30, 1967; Law Reporter on Carroll; Depositions; Plaintiffs-Appellees (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Brittan, Risdon v. Arons, Max, Local 802, AFM; 69 Civ. 4369; By-Laws. 1969 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Glasel, John v. Arons, Max, Local 802, AFM; 70 Civ. 860; Index (Partial); Correspondence, Mar 10, 1964; Summons & Complaint, Mar 3, 1970; Answer, 1964, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Memoranda for Summary Judgment; Judicial Decision, C.B. Motley, July 7, 1970; Plaintiff's Pre-Trial Memorandum (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Defendant's Pre-Trial Memoranda; Trial Memoranda, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Depositions, Defendants, Je 7, 1974; Stipulation, Dismissal, Jan 27, 1976, 1974, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Robert Greenfield v. Local 802, AFM; 71 Civ. 1923; Court Papers, Oct 10, 1969; Correspondence, R. Greenfield, Oct 28, 1971, 1923, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 21)